<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[The Hancock Journey]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[The Hancock Journey]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/hancockjourney/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2016 18:57:28 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/hancockjourney/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Road to Kapin]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The Road to Kapin</h1><p>The day we left the SIL compound to the Kapin village was a whirlwind.  We left around 8:30 in a truck that carried our gear.  I sat in in the back of the truck for about 4.5 hours and sat in the cab for 15 – 30 minutes.  The truck was halted a couple of times for a flat tire, flooding in the roads, and our last stop.  Then we hiked for 30mins uphill and I was totally bushed. When we came to the entrance to the village we saw a gate made from palm branches. Then we heard from the inside part of the gate the voice of the guard who said in his Pidgin talk “For what reason have you come?” The translator John Lindstrom cried  “We come in the name of Jesus!”  The guard replied…”since we do not know him you can come in so we can learn about him.” Apparently this was a re-enactment of what happen year ago. The gate was opened and guitar playing and singing started leading us into a procession. We were greeted by warm handshaking, wide smiles, and flowers wrapped around our neck. When we entered into the meeting room we saw girls with mango paint on their faces singing and throwing flower pedals at us…we were covered. Now there were three things that I learned  (I have learned this earlier but I have refused to…my skin does not react well with the sun so close to the equator.  I brought the suntan lotion with me but I forgot to take it to Kapin.  So I put a little on my face and arms and I thought I was good.  Well my knees got the sun and now I am hurting….and healing. The second thing is…hiking does not mean flat land.  I am sure I knew that it was going to be hilly but my mind was thinking that it would be a gradual incline.  Boy, was I wrong.  At times we had 6 inches of slippery path and then drop off.Third and final….I cannot do this alone.  I know Jesus was providing aid for my physical strength to hike to the village (and taking breaks as I went) but He also gave me the strength to keep on going and not quit.  You see…if I did not continue on going…I would have never completed the work that was given to me and I would never have received the prize or the opportunity to be greeted by the wonderful Kapin people.  I will always ponder of the road to Kapin as I think more of the road to Heaven. Thank you all for being a part of this journey by praying and financially giving to our family. What a way to celebrate Thanksgiving! Isaiah 40:31  …but they who wait for the Lord shall renew their strength;  they shall mount up with wings like eagles; they shall run and not be weary; they shall walk and not faint</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/8b1ce7e40f6696dfcd4649dae56543ef07479879.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/hancockjourney/the-road-to-kapin/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0c50f449-423e-42db-97d8-76e21ecfd91d</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2016 18:57:04 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Home]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Home</h1><p>Kapin</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/fbb864c40ec73d7d710adeb24966cb8cc0447780.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/hancockjourney/5e4ac9ae-d4c6-44eb-8c08-79ad16a58b83/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5e4ac9ae-d4c6-44eb-8c08-79ad16a58b83</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2016 18:52:21 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>